目覚めても　目覚めても　届かない
Mezametemo mezametemo todokanai
Even after awakening and awakening, it’s unreachable
結末に見慣れてしまいそうなほど
Ketsumatsu ni minarete shimaisou na hodo
To the point it seems I’m getting used to seeing the end
また一つ　また一つ　消えていく
Mata hitotsu mata hitotsu kiete yuku
Yet another, yet another disappears
増えすぎた犠牲　無機質な影
Fue sugita gisei mukishitsu na kage
Too many sacrifices, an inorganic shadow
どこかに置き去りにした
Dokoka ni okizari ni shita
Left behind somewhere,
正しさも　躊躇いも
Tadashisa mo tamerai mo
the righteousness and the hesitation
まるで何もなかったように
Marude nanimonakatta you ni
Like as if nothing has happened,
確実に仕留めるの
Kakujitsu ni shitomeru no
I’ll definitely bring it down
閉ざしかけた唇　触れて　繋いで
Tozashi kaketa kuchibiru furete tsunaide
Nearly closed lips, touching and connecting
唯一の望み以外　何も惜しくはないの
Yuiitsu no nozomi igai nanimo oshiku wa nai no
Other than the only hope, I do not hold anything else dear
優し過ぎるあなたの為なら
Yasashi sugiru anata no tame nara
If it’s for you who are too gentle
何度でも捧げましょう
Nando demo sasagemashou
Dedicating it over and over again.
諦めてくれるなら
Akiramete kureru nara
If you would give up…
Nii-sama Fansubs
Flashing Thunder Wave
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Unfashionable clothes. I'll buy you something new.
Oh? Those clothes will be fun to take off later
Cute clothes. They look good on you.
Episode 01
Nii-sama Fansubs
Don't Panic. It's a Spirit's Trap.
It was something nice and sweet
’til I see the real
It’s been always something cruel
dark and sore
近付くたび　煌めくたび　この胸　押し寄せる
Chikazuku tabi kirameku tabi kono mune oshiyoseru
Every time you get close, every time it glistens, it weighs upon this chest.
嬉しいでも苦しい　ここから先は　無理に近付かないで
Ureshii demo kurushii koko kara saki wa muri ni chikazukanaide
I’m happy but it’s painful. Don’t force your way any closer than this
やさしい声で
yasashii koe de
In a gentle voice
ただこのままでいたいだけ
Tada kono mama de itai dake
Even though all I want is to stay
揺さぶらないで
yusaburanaide
don’t shake me up
なのに
na no ni
like this
誰も崩せない
Daremo kuzusenai
Unbreakable by anyone,
築き上げた防壁-バリケード-
kizukiageta barikeedo
a built-up barricade
固く閉ざしてたはずだったのにどうして
Kataku tozashiteta hazu datta no ni doushite
It should have been firmly closed so why…
Do you hear weary heart’s S.O.S？
Do you hear weary heart’s S.O.S?
Episode 2                                 'So Be It! 2D It is!'